Fayo Yassien





(587) 227-7574



f.eshraaqah@hotmail.com

SUMMARY

A multilingual and cheerful customer services representative with 3+ years of experience in the graphic design field. Eager and self-motivated to benefit the community with my skills and knowledge, and acquire new experiences to continue developing.

SKILLS

- Excellent communication skills.
- Fast learner.
- Good at following instructions.
- Effective computer skills.
- Friendly, cooperator and good team player.
- Organized worker and ability to multitask.
- Ability to speak / write in Arabic, English and Oromo.

WORK EXPERIENCES

- Barista at Starbucks (from 9/2019 until now)
 - Preparing coffee and making beverages.
 - Customer services and casher.
- Freelancer (2014)
 - Preparing lessons as PowerPoint presentations.
 - Writing worksheets and some documents.
- Management assistant at a school (2015)
 - Archiving Organizer.
 - Arranging administrative student documents.
- Graphic Designer at the International Company for Food and Consumables IFCG – Egypt (from 8/2016 to 5/2019)
 - Design packages for frozen potato and vegetables, truck's posters, business cards, banners, catalog, carton boxes ...etc.

HOBBIES

- Arabic Calligraphy.
- Creating Designs.
- Reading Arabic Poems.
- Literary narrating in Arabic (writing stories for children and poetic attempts).

EDUCATION

- ICDL + Java Basics certificate obtained from the International Institute of Advanced Women Jeddah/Saudi Arabia.
- Ticketing certificate obtained from Cairo Wireless Institute.
- Graphic Design certificate obtained from Russian Cultural Center.
- First Aid certificate.
- Qur'an, Tajweed and Arabic at Dar Al Argam Institute.
- English for Academic Purposes at Bow Valley Collage.
- New Media Production and Design at SAIT (since May 2022 until now).

SOCIAL ACTIVITIES

- Editor of a school newspaper (2013)
 - Writing, organizing and designing school newspapers.
- Trainer at Dar Al-Argam (from 2015 to 2018)
 - Preparing and presenting summer activities and programs for young girls.
- Graphic Designer at Youth Radio (2016)
 - Designing Facebook posters.
 - Photoshop trainer for Design Department at the radio.
 - Microsoft Word/PowerPoint trainer for radio members.
- Graphic Designer at Dar Al-Argam (2018)
 - Designing ID cards for teachers and students.
 - Writing booklets and designed their covers.
 - Designing radio devices' boxes and their catalogs.

REFERENCES

Available upon request